let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "How do you instantiate an array in Java?",
    answer: "int arr[] = new int[3];",
    options: [
      "int arr[] = new int(3);",
      "int arr[];",
      "int arr[] = new int[3];",
      "int arr() = new int(3);",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "When does the ArrayIndexOutOfBoundsException occur?",
    answer: "Run-time",
    options: [
      "Compile-time",
      "Run-time",
      "Not an error",
      "Not an exception at all"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Process of removing an element from stack is called __________",
    answer: "Pop",
    options: [
      "Create",
      "Push",
      "Evaluation",
      "Pop"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is not the application of stack?",
    answer: "Data Transfer between two asynchronous process",
    options: [
      "A parentheses balancing program",
      "Tracking of local variables at run time",
       "Compiler Syntax Analyzer",
       "Data Transfer between two asynchronous process"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The data structure required for Breadth First Traversal on a graph is?",
    answer: "Queue",
    options: [
      "Stack",
      "Array",
      "Queue",
      "Tree"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Queues serve major role in ______________",
    answer: "Simulation of limited resource allocation",
    options: [
      "Simulation of recursion",
      "Simulation of arbitrary linked list",
      "Simulation of limited resource allocation",
      "Simulation of heap sort"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "A linear collection of data elements where the linear node is given by means of pointer is called?",
    answer: "Linked list",
    options: [
      "Linked list",
      "Node list",
      "Primitive list",
      "Unordered list"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " In linked list each node contains a minimum of two fields. One field is data field to store the data second field is?",
    answer: "Pointer to node",
    options: [
      "Pointer to character",
      "Pointer to integer",
      "Pointer to node",
      "Node"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The number of edges from the node to the deepest leaf is called _________ of the tree.",
    answer: "Height",
    options: [
      "Height",
      "Depth",
      "Length",
      "Width"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the average case time complexity for finding the height of the binary tree?",
    answer: "h = O(log n)",
    options: [
      "h = O(loglogn)",
      "h = O(nlogn)",
       "h = O(n)",
      "h = O(log n)"
    ]
  },
];